britainexpress.com 2019-05-29

# Britain Express Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Britain Express uses and protects any information that you give Britain Express when you use this website.

BritainExpress.com is a website owned and operated by Britain Express Limited. Registered company number: 5251831, Registered Address: Lower Ground Floor, 85 London Road, Cheltenham GL52 6HL, United Kingdom

Britain Express is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Britain Express may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25 May 2018 under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

### What does this policy cover?

This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of our website. Our website contains links to other websites that are owned and operated by third parties. Once you use these links to leave our website we have no control or responsibility over how your data is collected, stored, or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them. This includes all websites where you book accommodation or event or attraction tickets or memberships.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Information you send to us via our contact form, by email, by post, by telephone. This may include your name, your contact information including email, address and postcode, your shipping contact details (if different), your country of residence (if needed for VAT processing purposes), your financial data.
  * Technical data: Please note that we cannot identify you from this information. It may include your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website. We also collect information on which pages you visit and how you move through our website. (please see our cookie policy below)

### How is your personal data collected?

You may give us your information when you correspond with us. We may also receive anonymised personal data about you from various third parties as set out below:

**Technical Data from the following parties:**

  * analytics providers such as Google based outside the EU
  * advertising networks based inside or outside the EU

### What we do with the information we gather?

We require this information to provide you with a better service, and also for the following reasons:

  * to correspond with you. (We do not send marketing emails)
  * to process and send you orders
  * for legal, financial, and regulatory obligations
  * to improve our website and services

### Disclosure of your personal information

We may share your personal information with selected third parties for the purpose of processing your order. These would include business partners and suppliers inside or outside the EU. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

### How we protect your personal information

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How long do we keep your personal information?

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, and for managing any ongoing relationship with you.

We may use anonymised data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) indefinitely for research or to improve our website and products.

## Controlling your personal information:

Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you have the right to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you. We will process any request in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation. Please write to us at:

Britain Express Limited   
12 Sopwith Road   
Upper Rissington   
Cheltenham, GL54 2NS   
United Kingdom 

You also have the right to ask us to delete the information we hold about you where there is no good reason for us to retain it. Please write to us at the above address.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use session cookies to ensure your computer remembers where you've been on our website, enable you to use the shopping cart, and use e-commerce services. Session cookies are automatically deleted when you close your browser.

#### Third Party Cookies

We use third parties to either provide additional services on the website (such as Facebook Like buttons) or to track webpage traffic anonymously (such as Google Analytics) in order to improve our website and tailor it to customer needs. Some of these services will set cookies while you're on our website, but may also use these cookies for their own purposes. Britain Express Limited does not have direct control over these websites or cookies.

#### Google Analytics cookies

We use the Google Analytics suite to know what’s happening on our website. This tells us the number of visitors, what area of the world they are from, and how visitors move around on the site. This helps us improve the way the site works.

#### Google Advertising Services (e.g. AdSense, Doubleclick)

Google uses cookies to serve ads based on a user's previous visits to websites. Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of personalised advertising by visiting [Google Ad Settings](https://adssettings.google.co.uk/ "Google Ad Settings"). 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Britain Express Limited as specified above.
